hey everybody welcome to this a2 English
listening practice video you can use
this video to practice your listening
and comprehension as I speak you ready
so today I'm going to talk about clothes
and fashion this is a topic that I don't
really like that much but it's an
important one everybody wears clothes
and everybody has some kind of fashion
or lack of fashion I might be one of
those people that lacks fashion but
we'll get into that in a minute
first let's talk about when we first
develop our own fashion sense and take
it seriously for me this was around the
time when I was in middle school middle
school is when I started paying
attention to what kind of clothes I was
wearing what brands what styles and what
colors one of the first phases that I
went through was the one where I wore
really baggy clothes baggy clothes are
clothes that are too big for you and
they come down lower than normal clothes
my shirts were too long and my pants
weren't pulled up high enough it wasn't
a good phase for me I'm sure many of you
can remember going through something
like this when you were young if we look
back at our middle school pictures some
of us would be horrified so once I got
into high school my style changed
because I started playing more
basketball
thus I started buying all kinds of Air
Jordans Nikes and other brands of
basketball shoes I used to match the
color of my shoes with the color of my
shirts
I was super color-coordinated then after
that I ditched the basketball phase and
I started wearing more casual clothes
and then finally by the time I started
college I'd stopped caring so much about
what clothes I wore nowadays I'm the
least stylish person you'll meet I wear
what's comfortable and I don't have many
clothes so now let's talk about some of
the popular clothing stores that are out
there back when I was 17 I got my first
job at a clothing store called Hollister
some of you might know this store
actually it was really popular back in
my high school days but I don't know how
popular it is now now when I go shopping
I either go to stores like H&M or I go
to department stores like JCPenney
department stores are really big stores
that sell all kinds of clothes jewelry
electronics and other things from many
different brands
I like these stores because they have a
huge selection of clothes some of the
most popular athletic clothing stores in
the US include Nike footlocker and
Dick's Sporting Goods for woman
forever21 sada and Abercrombie & Fitch
are some of the popular stores do you
have these stores in your country in the
u.s. most popular clothing stores are
found in shopping malls here we just
call them malls you can find malls
everywhere in the u.s. I think most of
them are indoor malls but there are
plenty of outdoor malls too I'm not a
big fan of malls but there are
definitely times when I need to go there
to buy something and during the
Christmas season I have to spend much
more time at the mall buying presents
for everyone ok that's all for today
leave a comment and tell me what your
favorite clothing store is I'll see you
next time
[Music]
[Applause]